IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000000	Basic Operations
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000001	This section will continue were the Info-Pang left off.  You can expect a more in-depth explanation of the game mechanics and some unique features.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000002	If you read through this section and you still have questions you should visit the Official Website and Discord.  These can be found at http://en-flyff.boraecosystem.com/
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000003	Mouse 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000004	Your mouse will be used constantly throughout game play.  Left Clicking your mouse will be used most commonly for movement, targeting, and selecting menu options.  The Right Click will be used predominately for controlling the camera and accessing the NPC Menu when a NPC is targeted.  All of these features will be covered in the Help Menu.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000005	Movement
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000006	To move using the keyboard, press the “W” Key to go forward, the “A” Key to go left, the “S” Key to go backwards, and the “D” Key to go right.   You can also use the Left Click of the Mouse to move.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000007	To jump, simply press the spacebar.  You can jump either from a standing position or while moving.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000008	Camera
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000009	You can control the camera view in many different ways.  You can even lock the camera into place.  To do this access the Start Menu, select Option and then toggle Camera Fix.  This will allow you to control the Camera with the A and D keys.  This overrides movement controls.  If this setup does not feel comfortable to you, you can simply hold down the Right Mouse Button and move the mouse.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000010	Regardless of how you choose to manipulate the camera, the zoom functions will always be the same.  You can Zoom in and out with the mouse wheel or the Page Up and Page Down keys.  In order to zoom in even further, press the Scroll Lock Button.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000011	Flying
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000012	A character that has reached level 20 and has finished the flying quest can take advantage of flying with broom and boards.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000013	Station NPC's sell a variety of Brooms and Boards. If you feel like you would like to spice up your method of flying you can check the premium shop for faster and more unique items to fly on.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000014	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000015	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000016	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000017	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000018	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000019	How do I fly?
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000020	To fly, simply equip a flying board or broom and then press the Spacebar. You will automatically accelerate until your reach your maximum speed.  To stop, press the Spacebar again. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000021	You can steer while flying with your mouse or with the W,A,S,D keys.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000022	You can buy fuel to increase the speed of your broom or board. Double-click the fuel and press the X key to activate or de-activate the fuel.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000023	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000024	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000025	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000026	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000027	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000028	Combat
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000029	You will encounter hundreds of hostile masquerpets in the land of Madrigal.  Depending on what type of character you build, you will have multiple options on how to attack these villainous monsters.  These methods will be explained in more detail here.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000030	Along with these masquerpets, you can engage in intense PVP Combat if you have chosen to play on Demian.  To attack players on Demian, you must hold down the Ctrl Key and then initiate your attack. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000031	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000032	Melee Attack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000033	Melee attacks are done with all variations of close combat weapons, this includes swords, axes, staffs, and even knuckle weapons.  To engage a enemy in a Melee attack simply equip your weapon, target your enemy, and then Right  Click on them. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000034	Raged Attack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000035	Ranged attacks are done with Yo-yos, and bows.  To engage an enemy with a ranged attack, equip the appropriate weapon, target the enemy, and then Right Click on the target.    Note that Bow require arrows to be used.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000036	Magic Attack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000037	Wands have the unique ability to shoot a charged magic attack.  Do this by holding down the Right Mouse button after you have selected your target.  Release the button to launch your attack.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000038	Equipping items
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000039	To equip an item, open your inventory then double click the item you want to equip. It will then automatically replace the item you currently have equipped in that slot. Double click on equipped item to unequip it.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000040	Using Items
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000041	You can use an item by double clicking it. You can also place items in your Extra Bags by simply opening them and then dragging it over. The item drops to the ground if you place the item outside your inventory.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000042	You can place an item in the quick task bar located at the bottom of your screen. It is possible to use it instantly with the corresponding Hot Key or by clicking with your Mouse. Right click an item to remove the item from the quick slot.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000043	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000044	Chatting
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000045	Pressing enter will toggle the Chat Menu display on if you have closed it for any reason.  Once the Chat Menu is open simply press Enter one time to toggle the chat function.  Once you have typed your message simply press Enter again to send your message out.  You will also see buttons for Whisper, Shout, Party, and Guild.  These buttons will filter your message directly to those respective groups.  There are also options for filtering your incoming chats, and viewing System Messages.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000046	NPC Trading
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000047	To trade with an NPC, left click the NPC and choose Trade. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000048	You can purchase an item you want by dragging it into your inventory. The price of the item will show and if you accept the price a confirmation window will pop-up. Accept the confirmation window to finish the transaction.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000049	 If you are trying to sell items, just drag the item you want to sell from your inventory, into the NPC trade window.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000050	Player Trading 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000051	If you would like to trade with another player, you can hold down the ALT key and Left Click on the player, or simply Right Click on the player . A menu will appear, select trade, and wait for the other player to approve the trade.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000052	Once the trade window opens you can drag items or Penya into the window. Make very sure that everything is just how you want it before clicking OK and ACCEPT. Never let anyone BORROW any items as they may not return what you lend them. Make sure you are getting the right items and right amount of Penya before you go through with a trade. All trades are done at your own risk so please be very careful. If you lose something, get the wrong item, or the wrong Penya amount there is nothing that can be done to get the item back. So be careful. If at any time you feel uncomfortable with a trade click the CANCEL button to end the trade.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000053	Once you put items in a trade window and select OK and ACCEPT the trade will go through and the items you traded for will be in your inventory. If your inventory box is full the trade will be canceled.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000054	Quests
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000055	NPC's with a Yellow "!" above their heads have a Quest you can complete.  Select the NPC and then select New Quest.  This will show you all of the available quests and the level required to accept the quest.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000056	Complete as many quests as you can as they will give you many rewards along with valuable EXP bonuses!
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000057	Interface
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000058	This Section will detail the various Menus you will be seeing and using while you play.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000059	Status Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000060	You can toggle this window by pressing the T Button.  This Window will give you the overall status of your character.  It includes your Health Points, Magic Points, Focus Points, Experience, and Bubble Time.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000061	 Your total HP increases as you increase STA, the more HP you have the longer you will live.  MP is necessary for magician and assist skills. Your total MP increases as you increase your INT. FP is necessary for the melee attack skills of a mercenary, your total FP increases as you increase your STA.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000062	EXP notes the necessary amount of experience needed to level up. EXP is gained by hunting monsters and completing quests.  Bubble Time is a special Buff that gives you bonus EXP.  This is filled through the Guild House and is explained under that section of the Help Menu. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000063	Character Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000064	This Menu can be toggled with the H Key.  It displays important information about the character.  The Base Section displays basic information such as character name, job, level, etc... The Detail Section displays the character status according to the currently used equipment and level, and PVP/PK tracks your PVP information.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000065	When you gain levels you will be award STAT Points.  These can be spent on this Menu.  STAT Points are gained as you level up, and you can increase your base abilities. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000066	ATK represents your Attack Power, this is how much damage you can deliver to the enemy.  DEF represents your Defense, this is how much damage you can absorb from an enemy's attack.  Critical means how much chance you have to make a critical attack, and A. Speed shows how fast your character will attack.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000067	STR affects the attack power of all melee weapons.  STA affects defense, max HP, max FP, and HP/FP restoration. DEX affects attack speed, dodge, blocking, critical chance and bow attack power. INT affects maximum MP, MP restoration, magical spell damage and defense.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000068	The Fame/Master Tab will display of all the Titles you have earned.  Select one of these Titles to show the world what you can accomplish!
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000069	Chat Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000070	Press Enter to activate this Menu and then you can type in it. Chat, Whisper, Shout, Party and Guild Chats are possible. You can click the System button to view any system messages that have been displayed.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000071	If you want to copy a message and paste it with the Shortcut key then type the message into the chat window, don’t press enter, then drag the balloon mark located on the left side of the chat window to your quick slot. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000072	Navigator
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000073	Press the N Button to toggle this Menu. The Navigator is the mini-map located at the upper-right of your screen. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000074	NPC's will appear as purple dots, while other players will appear as white dots.  NPC Shops will be displayed with an icon that indicates what shop they are.  If you are turning in a quest look for a yellow and black dot.  Yellow and orange dots indicate enemy mobs.  If you use your mouse to roll over a dot, it will tell you the name of that specific target. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000075	There are a few buttons on the Mini-Map to help you as well.  You can zoom the mini-map in and out using the + and - icons.  The drop down will allow you to filter what appears on your Mini-Map. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000076	Skill Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000077	Toggle this Menu with the K Button.  This window displays the skills and skill tree of your character. You can upgrade skills if you have the necessary requirements.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000078	To use skills, drag the skill to the quick slots in the bottom center of the screen and use F1 - F9. Otherwise, drag the skill in the skill window to the Action Slot on the bottom right of the screen and press C.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000079	Skill points are necessary to level up your skill. Skill points are earned as you level up. Click the skill you want to increase and adjust the skill level with +,- button and click Finish.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000080	Inventory
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000081	Your inventory shows you everything you currently have equipped and everything you are carrying.  You can store weapons, armor, items, Penya and anything that isn't nailed down inside your inventory.  View your inventory by Pressing the I Button. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000082	Messenger Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000083	You can talk to friends and Guildies as well as check their current connection status. It will be updated as you add friends and guild members. To add your friend, hold down ALT and left click the character, then select ‘add to my list’ or click the + icon located below the messenger window. Your Guild list will automatically update as players come and go.  There is also a Tab to check you Mentor Pupil Status but that system is outlined later in the Help Guide.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000084	Quest Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000085	By pressing the Q Button, you can check the progress of your current quests and other valuable information about your quests. This Menu is divided into tabs to better help you organize your quests.  If you select a quest from the list it will be added to your on screen display to help you better track your progress quickly. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000086	Motion Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000087	This window displays emoticons and motion icons. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000088	You can activate this Menu by clicking the hot key 'o'. You can left click the icon to use it instantly or drag it the shortcut window and use it later.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000089	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000090	Party Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000091	This window manages your party. There are basic parties and advanced parties. Basic parties are groups that you share exp and items with, while an advanced party uses various party skills. When a basic party reaches level 10 you can change it to an advanced party and use party skills.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000092	Guild Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000093	A Guild is a bigger community then a party and anyone level 40 or higher can create one. You have to complete the quest from NPC Helena to make a guild. The Info tab shows general information and notices, the member tab allows you to manage guild members, the title tab shows titles and allows you to pay members, and the duel tab shows info on your guild duels.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000094	Options Tab
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000095	This window configures the basic details and options for the Game and can be found in the Start Tab.  There are many settings here and they have been separated into two Tabs: Video and Game / Audio.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000096	Video 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000097	This window is for video settings. If you set the options to their highest settings you may encounter some additional lag.  You will also see other settings for various visual elements.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000098	Game / Audio
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000099	From this tab you can allow or block Trades, Whispers, Friend Requests, Duel Requests, Party Requests, along with numerous other options.  You can also control the audio levels and Battle Music.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000100	Helper Tab
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000101	Selecting the Help Tab from the Start Menu will open various help texts.  You can find all forms of helpful things in this area.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000102	Help
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000103	This selection includes the Helper Tree you are currently looking at.  There are numerous topics here that are described in detail to help give you a better understanding of the game.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000104	Tips
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000105	This selection contains tips that help with game play and other things that are easily overlooked.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000106	FAQ
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000107	This is the FAQ window. When you have questions you should start here as there are numerous answers to various questions.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000108	Information Tab
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000109	This tab will give you access to the In-Game notice.   Various information and major news will be listed here from time to time.  This notice is also displayed by default when the game launches. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000110	Revive Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000111	This window opens when your HP reaches 0. There are three options, 'Lodestar' which allows you to revive from the nearest town.  If you have a 'Scroll of Resurrection' you can revive from the spot with the 'Original Place' option.  You can also visit the Cash item shop through this menu.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000112	Trade Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000113	If you either initiate a Trade or Accept another players Trade Request, you will be presented with this menu.  From here you can trade Penya and other various items.  The trade will have to be confirmed before it is completed. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000114	Bank Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000115	This Menu will allow you to store various items and Penya without taking up space in your inventory.  You can access your bank from the [Public Office] NPC in each major city.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000116	Task Bar
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000117	This section refers to the bar that runs along the bottom of your screen.  It houses your Start Menu, System Slots, and Quick Action Slots.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000118	Start Menu
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000119	This Menu allows the user to access all of the game options and various game play functions.  Many of the Hot Keyed Menus can be accessed through the Start Menu.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000120	System Slots
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000121	This refers to the slots to the right of the Start Menu.  These slots are used so that users can quickly access skills, save text strings, or other various tasks they want to repeat.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000122	Hot Keys
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000123	This refers to the nine slots in the middle of the bottom bar labeled F1-F9.  These slots are linked to the corresponding Function keys and can be triggered accordingly.  Reserve these for your most important funtions!
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000124	Action Slot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000125	The Action Slot is located in the lower right corner of the screen.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000126	What is the Action Slot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000127	The Action Slot allows you to trigger a pre-determined set of skills.  You can place skills in the Action Slot from the Skills Menu.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000128	Using the Action Slot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000129	To actually use the Action Slot you will need to select a target and press "C".  This can be done repeatedly.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000130	Order of the Action Slot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000131	Skills can be used in a succession as long as you follow the order of the different types of skills. The order is; Step > Circle > Finish. You can only use the action icons if the skills are in order.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000132	Action Slot Cooldown
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000133	There is a Cooldown for the Action Slot.  As you cast you will notice a shadow the will begin covering the Action Slot.  You will not be able to uses Skills that are covered in shadow.  Simply wait and the shadow will vanish.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000134	Community
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000135	In order to make Flyff more social and entertaining we encourage users to band together.  There is both an intricate Party System and a Guild System.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000136	Basic Party System
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000137	Parties are used to help benefit users who band together for a short time.  There are numerous benefits to joining a Party as opposed to playing alone.  The Party Menu can be accessed by pressing "P".
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000138	Party Requirements
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000139	To make a party, at least 2 people are needed. There are no job or level requirements to create normal party.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000140	Inviting members to a Party
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000141	To invite a player, either hold the ALT key and left click on the player or simply right click on the user. After accessing the Player Menu, simply select "Invite to join party".
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000142	Joining a Party
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000143	Select ACCEPT when you are invited to join a party.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000144	Leave a Party
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000145	To leave a Party, open the Party Menu and click on the LEAVE button. A Party will be disbanded automatically if everyone leaves the Party.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000146	Removing a Party member
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000147	Only the Leader of the Party can remove a Party member.  To do this you need to access the Party Menu, select the targeted Party member, and then finally press the Leave Button. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000148	Changing Party Leader
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000149	To transfer leadership in a Basic Party the Leader must choose a Party member and click the Transfer button. In case the Leader leaves the party, then the Party member placed next to Leader becomes the Party Leader.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000150	Become an Advanced Party
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000151	When a basic Party’s level reaches 10 it is able to change to an Advanced Party. Simply select the Change button on the Party Menu. Once your Party changes to an Advanced Party you will be able to name your Party.  Once you have an Advanced Party you can begin to take advantage of the Skills Tab inside the Party Menu.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000152	Advanced Party System
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000153	Advanced Parties evolve from Basic Parties.  They are very beneficial for groups attempting to conquer the most difficult tasks!
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000154	Become an Advanced Party
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000155	When a basic Party’s level reaches 10 it is able to change to an Advanced Party. Simply select the Change button on the Party Menu. Once your Party changes to an Advanced Party you will be able to name your Party.  Once you have an Advanced Party you can begin to take advantage of the Skills Tab inside the Party Menu.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000156	Inviting members to a Party
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000157	To invite a player, either hold the ALT key and left click on the player or simply right click on the user. After accessing the Player Menu, simply select "Invite to join party".
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000158	Joining an advanced party.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000159	Select ACCEPT when you are invited to join a party.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000160	Party EXP and Skills
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000161	The Advanced Party will get stronger as your Party earns EXP which in turn gives the Party Points. These Party Points are then consumed to use Party Skills. The Party Skills and Points are different according to the level of the Party.  Only the Party Leader can use the Party Skills. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000162	Leave a Party
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000163	To leave a Party, open the Party Menu and click on the LEAVE button. A Party will be disbanded automatically if everyone leaves the Party.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000164	Removing a Party member
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000165	Only the Leader of the Party can remove a Party member.  To do this you need to access the Party Menu, select the targeted Party member, and then finally press the Leave Button. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000166	Changing Party Leader
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000167	To transfer leadership in an Advanced Party the Leader must choose a Party member and click the Transfer button. In case the Leader leaves the party, then the Party member placed next to Leader becomes the Party Leader.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000168	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000169	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000170	Advanced Party Skills
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000171	Only the Advanced Party Leader can use the Advanced Party Skills. The Advanced Party Skills will be acquired as you reach a certain Party Level. Party Points are consumed to use Skills.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000172	Call Out
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000173	Informs all Party members of the location of the Party Leader. It does not consume any Party Skill Points.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000174	Blitz
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000175	Party Leader orders Party members to attack a target. It does not consume any Party Skill Points.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000176	Retreat
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000177	Party Leader orders all Party members to retreat. It does not consume any Party Skill Points.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000178	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000179	
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000180	Precision
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000181	Use this ability to gain an almost guaranteed critical hit on your next attack. Available at party level 17, consumes 1 Party Skill Point.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000182	Link Attack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000183	While the Party Leader is attacking a target, damage increase for all Party members attacking the same target.  Available at party level 20, consumes 1 Party Skill Point.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000184	Lucky Drop
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000185	Increases the chance of Masquerpets dropping unique items. Available at party level 25, consumes 1 Party Skill Point.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000186	Resting
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000187	Party members recover 1.5 times faster.  It the Party Leader is an Assist, Party members recover 1.8 times faster. Available at party level 30, consumes 2 Party Skill Points.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000188	Treasure Hunter
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000189	Increases the amount of items dropped by Masquerpets. Available at party level 40, consumes 8 Party Skill Points.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000190	Jobs and their Skills
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000191	This section details the various Jobs in Flyff and all of their corresponding skills. The Skill Menu can be pulled up by pressing the K Key. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000192	Players will receive Skill Points as they Level up their characters.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000193	These Skill Points can then be assigned to various skills to increase the strength of that particular Skill. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000194	PH1
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000195	Vagrants are the basic class everyone in Flyff starts with before they decide on their First Job Change. They use physical attacks and use melee weapons like swords and axes.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000196	Clean Hit
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000197	A powerful, downward strike.  This skill is available at Level 3 and can be used with any Melee Weapon. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000198	Flurry
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000199	A rapid stabbing attack that follows a Clean Hit in the Action Slot. This skill is available at Level 5 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Clean Hit and can be used with any Melee Weapon.   
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000200	Over Cut
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000201	This attack gathers all of the power the vagrant has and unleashes it in a strong upwards finishing blow.  Over Cut completes the combo after Flurry in the Action Slot.  This skill is available at Level 10 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Flurry and can be used with any Melee Weapon.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000202	Mercenary
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000203	Mercenaries prefer to partake in close range combat. The main characteristics of this particular class involve physical strength, and a strong body that is able to withstand attacks.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000204	Powerful and headstrong, the mercenary has both inner and physical strength.   Mercenaries will become either a Blade or a Knight.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000205	PH2
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000206	Strikes the enemy two times, in rapid succession.  This skill is available at Level 15 and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000207	PH3
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000208	A continuous spinning attack.  This skill is available at Level 18 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Slash and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000209	PH4
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000210	A spinning, finishing move.  This skill is available at Level 24 to Players who have at least 6 Skill Points in Keenwheel and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000211	Special Hit
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000212	A single powerful strike.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 8 Skill Points in Blindside and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000213	PH5
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000214	Drains life from an enemy.   This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Slash and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000215	Hit Reflect
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000216	This Skill absorbs one attack and releases it back at an enemy.   This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 8 Skill Points in Bloody Strike and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000217	Guillotine
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000218	This attack begins from a short distance and then launches the player at the enemy in a fiery burst.   This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 10 Skill Points in Hit Reflect and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000219	Protection
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000220	Increases the defense of a Shield against melee attacks.   This skill is available at Level 15 and requires a shield.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000221	Pan Barrier
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000222	Increases the defense of a Shield against ranged attacks.  This skill is available at Level 18 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Protection and requires a shield.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000223	Sneaker
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000224	Holds an enemy in place with a net.  This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 10 Skill Points in Pan Barrier and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000225	Empower Weapon
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000226	This Skill strengthens the elemental damage of a weapon. It is not applied if there is no elemental attack power on the weapon.  This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Protection and can be used with any Axe or Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000227	Smite Axe
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000228	Increases the attack level of an Axe and gives additional defense.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Empower Weapon and can be used with any Axe.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000229	Axe Mastery
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000230	Increases the attack level of an Axe.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 9 Skill Points in Smite Axe and can be used with any Axe.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000231	Blazing Sword
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000232	Increases the attack level and accuracy of a Sword.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Empower Weapon and can be used with any Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000233	Sword Mastery
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000234	Increases the attack level of a Sword.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 9 Skill Points in Blazing Sword and can be used with any Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000235	Acrobat
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000236	Acrobats mainly wield long distance weapons such as Bows or Yo-Yos. Using tactics based on speed and accuracy, they are usually able to break anyone willing enough to fight them. Sly and witty, the acrobat is a cunning trickster. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000237	An Acrobat will use MP for Bow Skills and FP for Yo-Yo skills.  For universal skills like Dark Illusion, Acrobats use FP.  Acrobats will become either a Jester or a Ranger.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000238	Pulling
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000239	Pulls a target towards the player.  This skill is available at Level 15 to Players and can be used with any Yo-Yo.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000240	Fast Walker
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000241	Increases the walking speed of the user for a limited time.  This skill is available at Level 18 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Pulling and can be used with any Bow or Yo-Yo.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000242	Dark Illusion
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000243	Turn a character invisible for a short time.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 6 Skill Points in Fast Walker and can be used with any Bow or Yo-Yo.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000244	Perfect Block
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000245	Block rate will be increased.  This skill is available at Level 45 to Players who have at least 8 Skill Points in Dark Illusion and can be used with any Bow or Yo-Yo.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000246	Slow Step
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000247	You have a chance to decrease the moving speed of enemy.  This skill is available at Level 15 and can be used with any Yo-Yo. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000248	Yo-Yo Mastery
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000249	Increases Yo-Yo damage.  This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Slow Step and can be used with any Yo-Yo. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000250	Snatch
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000251	Steals Penya from the target; can only be used while in Dark Illusion from behind target.  This skill is available at Level 35 to Players who have at least 8 Skill Points in Yo-Yo Mastery and can be used with any Yo-Yo. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000252	Deadly Swing
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000253	A critical attack that has a chance to cause the enemy to bleed.  This skill is available at Level 50 to Players who have at least 10 Skill Points in Snatch and can be used with any Yo-Yo. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000254	Cross Line
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000255	Gather energy into your Yo-Yo in order to strike an enemy with a powerful attack that has the chance to stun your target.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 8 Skill Points in Yo-Yo Mastery and can be used with any Yo-Yo. .
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000256	Counterattack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000257	Evade the enemy's next attack and strike back with an attack of your own.  This skill is available at Level 40 to Players who have at least 10 Skill Points in Cross Line and can be used with any Yo-Yo. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000258	Rapid Shot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000259	This skill shoots four arrows very quickly but with reduced accuracy.  This skill is available at Level 15 and can be used with any Bow.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000260	Bow Mastery
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000261	Increases Bow damage.  This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Rapid Shot and can be used with any Bow.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000262	Silent Shot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000263	Delivers a powerful sneak attack to the target if you are in Dark Illusion.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Bow Mastery and can be used with any Bow.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000264	Auto Shot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000265	Attacks four times in succession without missing.  Each hit is slightly less damaging than a hit from Rapid Shot.  This skill is available at Level 45 to Players who have at least 9 Skill Points in Silent Shot and can be used with any Bow.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000266	Aimed Shot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000267	A carefully aimed shot that has a chance to deal double damage to the target.  This skill is available at Level 35 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Bow Mastery and can be used with any Bow.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000268	Arrow Rain
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000269	A rain of arrows that will fall on all enemies in a wide circle around your target.  This skill is available at Level 50 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Aimed Shot and can be used with any Bow.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000270	Assist
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000271	The Assist is the priest or medic of Flyff.  The two primary builds for this job are a Full Support healer or a Buff Warrior. Both have the same skills to chose from. Where the Healer will need a partner to level, the Warrior can self-buff and fight alone.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000272	The Assist may chose from Ringmaster or Billposter when the times comes to progress into a second Job.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000273	Heal
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000274	Primary healing spell, which recovers a portion of the target's HP.  This skill is available at Level 15 and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000275	Patience
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000276	Increases the target’s maximum HP.  This skill is available at Level 18 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Heal and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000277	Resurrection
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000278	Revives a dead Player, but only grants a portion of their HP.  This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Patience and can be used with any Stick.   
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000279	Circle Healing
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000280	Heals Party Members within a specified range of yourself.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Resurrection and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000281	Prevention
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000282	This spell will automatically recover all of your HP if you drop below 10% HP.   This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Circle Healing and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000283	Quick Step
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000284	Increases the target’s walking speed. The higher the level, the faster the target walks. This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Heal and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000285	Haste
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000286	Increases the attack speed of a target Player.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Quick Step and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000287	Cat's Reflex
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000288	Increases the Evasion rate of a target Player.   This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Haste and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000289	Cannon Ball
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000290	Increases the DEX of a target Player.   This skill is available at Level 35 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Cat's Reflex and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000291	Mental Sign
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000292	Increases the INT of a target Player.   This skill is available at Level 18 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Heal and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000293	Heap Up
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000294	Increases the STA of a target Player.  This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Mental Sign and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000295	Beef Up
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000296	Increases the STR of a target Player.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Heap Up and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000297	Accuracy
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000298	Increases the accuracy of a target player.   This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Beef Up and can be used with any Stick.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000299	Straight Punch
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000300	A powerful, straight punch that strikes the enemy with a concentrated attack.  This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Heal and can be used with any Knuckle.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000301	Stone Hand
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000302	Physical attacks gain the chance to stun the target.   This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Straight Punch and can be used with any Knuckle.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000303	Burst Crack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000304	Smashes the ground and inflicts damage to enemies within the surrounding area.  This skill is available at Level 28 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Stone Hand and can be used with any Knuckle.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000305	Power Fist
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000306	A concentrated powerful strike.  This skill is available at Level 35 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Burst Crack and can be used with any Knuckle.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000307	Magician
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000308	Magicians control powerful elemental magic with the use of wands or staves. Magicians benefit from high intelligence. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000309	Magicians will be able to advance in their Jobs to become either an Elementor or a Psykeeper.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000310	Mental Strike
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000311	Deals non elemental magic damage to the target. Damage dealt varies by the difference of INT between the caster and the target.  This skill is available at Level 15 and can be used with any Wand or Staff.   
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000312	Flame Ball
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000313	Strikes at the enemy with a ball of flame.  This skill is available at Level 18 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Mental Strike and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000314	Flame Geyser
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000315	Inflicts intermediate fire damage to the target with a lasting Damage Over Time effect.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Flame Ball and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000316	Fire Strike
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000317	Damages an enemy with a fire ball. The enemy loses health for a limited time afterwards.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 7 Skill Points in Flame Geyser and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000318	Swordwind
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000319	A violent wind that attacks a target from a short distance.   This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Mental Strike and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000320	Strongwind
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000321	A tornado of wind that deals damage to the target as well as pushing them back.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Swordwind and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000322	Wind Cutter
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000323	A blade of wind that deals damage to the target.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 7 Skill Points in Strongwind and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000324	Ice Missile
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000325	Inflicts basic water damage with a chance of slowing down the target’s movement.  This skill is available at Level 20 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Mental Strike and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000326	Waterball
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000327	Shoots damaging balls of water at the target. The number of balls fired increases as the skill level increases.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Ice Missile and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000328	Water Well
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000329	A spell that throws columns of water at the target, dealing a large amount of damage.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 7 Skill Points in Waterball and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000330	Static Ball
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000331	A spell that gathers static electricity and forms it into a small ball that causes basic lightning damage.  This skill is available at Level 18 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Mental Strike and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000332	Lightning Ram
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000333	Deals a medium amount of lightning damage to the target.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Static Ball and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000334	Lightning Shock
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000335	Damages the enemy with a small but fast lightning ball.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 7 Skill Points in Lightning Shock and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000336	Stone Spike
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000337	Inflicts earth elemental damage to the opponent as well as creating a chance to stun the target.  This skill is available at Level 18 to Players who have at least 2 Skill Points in Mental Strike and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000338	Rock Crash
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000339	Damages the enemy with a giant stone.  This skill is available at Level 25 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Stone Spike and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000340	Rooting
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000341	Harnesses the power of the ground to prevent a user from moving.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 7 Skill Points in Rock Crash and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000342	Blinkpool
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000343	Teleports the user in a specified location within the limited range. The range increases as the skill level goes up.  This skill is available at Level 30 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Mental Strike and can be used with any Wand or Staff.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000344	Power Stomp
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000345	Hits the ground with the handle of the axe. The shock wave deals damage with a chance to stun to all nearby enemies.  The damage and stun chance will increase with every Skill Level.  This skill is available at Level 65 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Pain Dealer and can be used with any two handed Axe.    
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000346	Knight
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000347	Mercenaries who chose to follow the teachings of the Hero Billeien become Knights.  Knights are capable of incredible defense and possess the power to withstand the greatest assaults.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000348	Charge
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000349	A melee attack that deals maximum damage to a monster regardless of its level.  This skill is available at Level 60 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Sword Mastery and can be used with any two handed Sword.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000350	Earth Divider
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000351	A skill which damages nearby enemies. Higher Skill Level will result in more damage.  This skill is available at Level 65 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Charge and can be used with any two handed Sword.    
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000352	Pain Dealer
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000353	A melee skill which damages the target as  lowering its defense.  Higher Skill Level will result in more damage and a bigger decrease in defense.  This skill is available at Level 60 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Axe Mastery and can be used with any two handed Axe.    
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000354	Guard
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000355	Increases the characters defense but reduces the characters attack power.  This skill is available at Level 62 and can be used with either a two handed Axe or Sword. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000356	Rage
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000357	Increases the characters attack power and HP, but it also reduces the characters defense and accuracy.  This skill is available at Level 65 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Guard and can be used with either a two handed Axe or Sword. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000358	Pain Reflection
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000359	Reflects a portion of damage you receive back at the target.  This skill is available at Level 70 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Rage and can be used with either a two handed Axe or Sword. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000360	Power Swing
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000361	A huge horizontal swing that deals damage, and knocks enemies back.  This skill is available at Level 75 to Players who have at least 7 Skill Points in Pain Reflection and can be used with either a two handed Axe or Sword. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000362	Blade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000363	Blades are a second class for mercenaries and are the best damage dealers in the game. As a blade you will be able to wield two weapons at the same time and thus drastically increase your damage output. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000364	Silent Strike
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000365	A melee skill which deals a vicious cut in a sliding motion to the enemy.  This skill is available at Level 60 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Sword Mastery and can be used with a one handed Sword.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000366	Blade Dance
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000367	Uses both swords to attack all of the enemies around the wielder.  This skill is available at Level 65 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Silent Strike and can be used with a one handed Sword.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000368	Spring Attack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000369	Strike at multiple enemies times.  This skill is available at Level 60 to Players who have at least 3 Skill Points in Axe Mastery and can be used with two one handed axes.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000370	Hawk Attack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000371	Jumps, striking the enemy with both weapons. Deals massive damage and possibly blinds the enemy for a short period of time.   This skill is available at Level 65 to Players who have at least 5 Skill Points in Silent Strike and can be used with two one handed axes.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000372	Armor Penetrate
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000373	A melee skill which ignores 50% of target's defense rating.  This skill is available at Level 62 and can be used with a one handed Sword or Axe.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000374	Berserk
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000375	Temporarily raises attack power and attack speed, but you can not use any skills for the duration of the spell.  This skill is available at Level 65 to Players who have at least 4 Skill Points in Armor Penetrate and can be used with a one handed Sword or Axe.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000376	Sonic Blade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000377	Gathers a powerful aura and transfers it to your weapon, and then deals damage to the closest enemy.  This skill is available at Level 70 to Players who have at least 7 Skill Points in Berserk and can be used with a one handed Sword or Axe.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000378	Cross Strike
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000379	A strong attack is dealt to the enemy with both weapons at once.  This skill is available at Level 75 to Players who have at least 7 Skill Points in Sonic Blade and can be used with a one handed Sword or Axe.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000380	Jester
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000381	The first job class for Acrobats, they specialize in strong attacks made with a Yo-yo.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000382	placholder 31
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000383	Critical swing
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000384	Increase the probability of a critical strike.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000385	Enchant Poison
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000386	Plastering poison on the weapon to increase the normal damage and available to infect the enemy with poision
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000387	Enchant Bleed
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000388	Increase the normal damage with the bleeding attribute and available to make the enemy bleeding.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000389	Enchant Absorb
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000390	You can drain the HP of enemy with striking.  The drain will be occurred with certain probability.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000391	Back Step
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000392	When attacking from behind, deals a critical strike to the enemy. Also has a chance to stun the enemy.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000393	Penya Strike
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000394	Uses a Yo-yo and a small amount of Penya to deal massive damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000395	Escape
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000396	Enables character to escape from any movement impairing effects.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000397	Vital Stab
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000398	While using Dark Illusion, allows for a sudden attack from the shadows.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000399	Ranger
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000400	The second job class for Acrobats, they specialize in long distance attacks, mainly with a bow.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000401	placholder 32
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000402	Fast Shot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000403	The attack sppeed will be increased for a certain time.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000404	Ice Arrow
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000405	This skill causes an explosion of frost, slowing all enemies in a certain area for a certain period of time.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000406	Flame Arrow
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000407	This skill causes an explosion of frost, slowing the enemy for a certain period of time.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000408	Piercing Arrow
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000409	This skill pierces monsters who are a straight line, dealing damage to all of them.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000410	Poison Arrow
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000411	The strong damage and continuous poisonous damage will be occurred simutaneously.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000412	Silent Arrow
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000413	Deals strong damage and silences the target. While silenced, the target cannot cast spells of any kind.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000414	Nature
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000415	Resistance against some elemental magic will be increased.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000416	Triple shot
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000417	Triple arrows will be shot to deal strong damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000418	Ringmaster
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000419	The first job class for Assists, uses a staff like an Assist. Focuses more on supporting party than damaging monsters.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000420	Protect
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000421	This buff increases the physical defense of the target.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000422	Holy Guard
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000423	This buff increases the elemental resistance or magical defense of the target.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000424	Holy Cross
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000425	The enemy will take double damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000426	Spiriture Fortune
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000427	Greatly increases your melee attack power for a period of time.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000428	Gebura Tiphreth
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000429	Increases accuracy, speed and attack power for all party members within range.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000430	Gvur Tialla
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000431	Cleanses any abnormal conditions.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000432	Heal Rain
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000433	Recovers a large amount of HP for all party members.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000434	Merkaba Hanzelrusha
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000435	Deals damage over time to all enemies in a certain area.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000436	Billposter
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000437	The second job class for Assists, they use a knuckle hammer like Assists. They specialize in Critical attacks but have a slower attack speed.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000438	Belial Smashing
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000439	A skill that delivers one powerful dashing punch.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000440	Blood Fist
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000441	Strikes the enemy, making it bleed. Bleeding causes additional damage over time.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000442	Piercing Serpent
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000443	Dashes forward with a burning fist, striking the enemy.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000444	Asmodeus
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000445	Increases the attack power bonus of knuckles.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000446	Baraqijal Esna
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000447	When the skill works, it reduces the monsters defense and increases the monsters attack power.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000448	Grvub Tialbold
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000449	An energy wave deals damage to all monsters around the caster.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000450	Sonic Hand
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000451	Uses a knuckle hammer to strike with deadly speed.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000452	Asalraalaikum
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000453	Strikes the enemy with concentrated power, consumes all MP.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000454	Elementor
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000455	The first job class for Magicians, they use staves like Magicians. They specialize in magic effecting large numbers of enemies at once.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000456	Firebird
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000457	A fireball strikes the enemy.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000458	Burning Field
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000459	Sheets of flame burn the enemy for a period of time.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000460	Fire Master
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000461	Increases damage done by fire skills.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000462	Stone Spear
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000463	A spear made of rock strikes the enemy.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000464	Earthquake
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000465	Make a huge earthquake which deals a large amount of damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000466	Earth Master
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000467	Increases damage done by earth skills.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000468	Void
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000469	Strong Wind damage is dealt to a single target.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000470	Windfield
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000471	A strong wind slows all enemies around the caster for a period of time.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000472	Wind Master
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000473	Increases damage done by wind skills.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000474	Thunder Strike
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000475	Strong Lightning damage is dealt to a single target.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000476	Electric Shock
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000477	Deals lightning damage to all enemies around the caster, also lowering their defense temporarily.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000478	Lightning Master
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000479	Increases damage done by lightning skills.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000480	Iceshark
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000481	A shark made of ice strikes the enemy.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000482	Poison Cloud
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000483	A poison cloud engulfs the enemy, dealing poison and wind damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000484	Water Master
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000485	Increases damage done by water skills.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000486	Meteo Shower
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000487	Meteors strike all the enemies in a certain area, dealing fire and earth damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000488	Lightning Storm
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000489	Lightning and wind damage is dealt to all enemies in the area of effect.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000490	Sandstorm
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000491	A sand storm strikes all the enemies in a certain area, dealing wind and earth damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000492	Avalanche
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000493	A blizzard strikes all the enemies in a certain area, dealing earth and water damage as well as stunning them.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000494	Psykeeper
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000495	The second job class for Magicians, they use a wand like a Magician. They specialize in magic attacks that assault the mind of the enemy.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000496	Demonology
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000497	Deals damage to the mind of the enemy, by creating illusions of devils.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000498	Satanology
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000499	Confuses the enemy, and binds them in place for a certain amount of time.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000500	Psychic Bomb
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000501	Builds up spiritual power, and releases it to do massive damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000502	Spirit Bomb
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000503	Collapse the spirit of the enemy, deals damage based on MP.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000504	Psychic Wall
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000505	Creates a psychic barrier in front of the caster that the monster cannot pass.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000506	Crucio Spell
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000507	Gives a certain chance to reflect skill and magic attacks, at double damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000508	Maximum Crisis
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000509	If it works then it deals huge damage to the monster. If not, the caster takes the damage instead.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000510	Psychic Square
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000511	Dazzles the monster and deals a large amount of damage.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000512	Information of the ability
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000513	This explains the information of various abilities that can be increased by growth of character.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000514	Name
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000515	The given name of the avatar/character.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000516	Job
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000517	This shows the job/class that the player has chosen for his character.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000518	Level
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000519	This increases according to the accumulated EXP gain, GP(Growing point) according to level up, and you can increases ability with GP.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000520	placholder 33
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000521	placholder 34
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000522	placholder 35
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000523	placholder 36
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000524	Strength
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000525	Weapon attack rate increases except for wands.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000526	Stamina
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000527	Affects HP, FP, Defense and HP/FP restoration rate.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000528	Dexterity
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000529	Affects accuracy, attack speed, dodge rate, block rate, critical chance and bow attack power.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000530	Intelligence
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000531	Affects maximum MP, MP restoration amount, magic power and magic defense.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000532	HP (life)
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000533	This is the vitality of the character and the character will die if it reaches 0. You can recover it with food and pill items.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000534	MP (spirit)
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000535	This is for using magic, you can revive it by drinking refresher.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000536	FP (endurance)
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000537	This is needed to use physical skills. It can be replenished by resting/sitting down but it can be immediately recovered by using vitality drink items.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000538	EXP (experience)
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000539	This is required to raise the level of a character. It can be earned by killing monsters or through quests.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000540	Skills
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000541	Skills get stronger as you level and put more points into them.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000542	Stat points
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000543	This is the point you get when you level up. You can distribute the points to your STR,STA,DEX, and INT.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000544	Extra ability
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000545	Some skills require you to become a Hero before being usable, and require special training to be leveled / trained.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000546	Attack
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000547	This shows the Attack Capacity of a character. The character’s equipment and supportive skills cast on the character also influences this.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000548	Defense
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000549	This shows the Defense Capacity of a character. The character’s equipment and supportive skills cast on the character also influences this.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000550	Critical hit rate
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000551	This means how much chance you have to make a critical hit.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000552	Speed
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000553	This shows the Attack Rate of a character when attacking.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000554	Resisting power
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000555	This indicates how much “Reduced/Weakened magical damage” a character can receive.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000556	Properties
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000557	There are 5 elemental properties or attributes that exist in FLYFF. Each of these properties has a strength and weakness. A player can achieve the highest possible damage when he uses a weapon which is imbued with the property that is the weakness of his enemy’s property.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000558	Fire
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000559	Fire A property that is weak against the Wind property but is weak against the Water property.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000560	Water
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000561	Water. A property that is as strong against the Fire Property but is weak against the Electricity property.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000562	Electricity
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000563	A property that is strong against the Water Property but weak against the Earth Property.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000564	Earth
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000565	earth A property that is strong against the Electricity Property but weak against the Wind Property.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000566	Wind
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000567	A property that is strong against the Earth Property but weak against the Fire property.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000568	Enchant
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000569	Upgrading means making the item more powerful. Each item can be normally upgraded over 10 levels, and weapons / armor chest pieces can be elementally upgraded over 20 levels.  If the upgrade fails, there is no penalty between levels 1 and 3,  but from levels 4-10, there is a chance the item will be lost.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000570	Attribute Enchant
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000571	Your item can receive an attribute modifier (visible in the name of the item) through various means, granting it extra STR, STA, DEX and/or INT. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000572	Fire Upgrade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000573	When you refine an item with the Fire property, you’ll need a Fire Property Card. When an item is imbued with the Fire Property the item becomes weak to Wind but stronger against Water.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000574	Water Upgrade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000575	When you refine an item with the Water property, you’ll need a Water Property Card. When an item is imbued with the Water Property the item becomes weak to Fire but stronger against Electricity.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000576	Electric Upgrade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000577	When you refine an item with the Electricity property, you’ll need an Electricity Property Card. When an item is imbued with the Electricity Property the item becomes weak to Water but stronger against Earth.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000578	Wind Upgrade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000579	When you refine an item with the Wind property, you’ll need a Wind Property Card. When an item is imbued with the Wind Property the item becomes weak to Earth but stronger against Fire.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000580	Earth Upgrade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000581	When you refine an item with the Earth property, you’ll need an Earth Property Card. When an item is imbued with the Earth Property the item becomes weak to Electricity but stronger against Wind.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000582	General Upgrade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000583	Normal upgrade means a non-element upgrade. Power Dice are required to upgrade, there are 5 types of Power Dice, 4, 6, 8, 10 and 12.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000584	Ultimate Weapon Upgrade
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000585	You can make an Ultimate Weapon with a +10 upgraded unique weapon by using the Ultimate Weapon Upgrade. The maximum upgrade for an Ultimate weapon is up to +10 the same as any other item upgrade but it needs 'Shining Orikalkum'. The Ultimate upgrade is available only for weapons, and the item is destroyed in case of a failure. From +6 you are able to socket your weapon.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000586	placholder 39
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000587	placholder 40
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000588	placholder 41
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000589	placholder 42
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000590	placholder 43
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000591	placholder 44
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000592	placholder 45
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000593	placholder 46
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000594	placholder 47
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000595	placholder 48
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000596	Building
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000597	Information about the buildings that provide services.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000598	Lodestar
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000599	This is a structure that gathers spiritual life and resurrects players who died. It is located inside a city or a wide open clearing.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000600	Lodelight
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000601	This is a structure that functions like a Lodestar but it resurrects a player in a place near the hunting grounds.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000602	Weapon shop
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000603	This place sells weapons for the 1st job class such as vagrant, mercenary, and acrobat. It also sells weapons for the 2nd job class such as knight, blade, ringmaster, billposter, jester, and ranger.  
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000604	Armor shop
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000605	This place sells armor for Mercenaries, Assists, and Acrobats.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000606	Magic store
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000607	This place sells weapons, armor, and magic items best suited for Magicians.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000608	Food shop
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000609	This shop sells food items that help recover HP
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000610	General merchandise
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000611	This place sells Arrows, Posters, and those sorts of things.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000612	Public Office
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000613	This place is for selling Perin, using your personal bank, and guild bank.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000614	Station
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000615	This shop sells Flight related items like Flight gears as well as guide’s player on how to fly.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000616	Duel
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000617	A duel is a battle between 2 players. This is different from PK. It is called PvP (Player Vs Player) which can only start when 2 players agree to a duel. A duel has no penalties associated with it.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000618	Fame
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000619	You will gain the fame if you keep winning duels. You will also gain  different titles as well.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000620	Guild Combat Center
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000621	This place is for applying and running guild sieges and 1 on 1 guild sieges. Only available on the 1st sub server.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000622	Other inquiries
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000623	Please visit the official homepage:  https://en-flyff.play2bit.com/ for more inquiries. Have a nice day.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000624	Beauty shop
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000625	You can change your hair style and color. The price varies based on the color and style you choose.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000626	Private Shop
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000627	Items can be conveniently presented for sale to through this option. You can set the quantity and the price.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000628	Open the Start menu, select Personal Shop, and the Personal Shop window will appear.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000629	Drag the items you wish to sell from your inventory and drop them into the Personal Shop window.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000630	After dragging the item into the window, you can set the price for the item, and the quantity you wish to sell.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000631	Put a name in the Shop Name Window, and press OK. You can start selling items after that.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000632	Creating a Guild
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000633	There are some basic requirements to creating a Guild.  You will need a party of three players all at least level 40, then you have to complete a quest through the Public office NPC Helena in SM. Once finished you and your party members will become a guild.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000634	Raising the Guild Level
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000635	Guild Members area able to contribute items and Penya towards raising the guild level.  To contribute items, simply press the Support Button inside of the Guild Storage.  Raising the Guild Level will open up various options to the Guild to help it grow and distinguish itself. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000636	Joining a Guild
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000637	Initially only a Guild Master has the authority to invite Guild members. But a Guild Master can give authority to any Guildie to recruit other members to his Guild.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000638	Disbanding a Guild
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000639	The Guild Master can disband the Guild by pressing the DISMISS button on the Guild Menu.  Once the Guild is dismissed, it takes 2 days before Members can create or join a new Guild.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000640	Managing Guild Members
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000641	The Guild Master can manage his Guild from the Guild Menu.  He can set things such as promotions, demotions, nicknames, kicking from Guild, etc. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000642	Managing Guild Ranks
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000643	The Guild Master can manage Guild Ranks in the Guild Menu. He can set the authority of the title, degree, admission, access to items and monthly payment.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000644	Announcement
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000645	Guild Masters can make an announcement by clicking the Notice button on the Information Tab in the Guild Menu.  Either a new message can be made of the old one can simply be modified. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000646	Guild Logo
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000647	The Guild Logo is the symbol or emblem of the Guild. This can be chosen only once and only by the Guild Master. To use this function, select the Logo button in the Guild Menu.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000648	Guild Storage
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000649	You can use the Guild Storage only on the 1st Channel of each Server. Anyone can deposit items and Penya into the Guild Storage but only authorized Guild Members can withdraw items and penya. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000650	Info-Pang
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000651	You may have noticed when you first logged into the game that you were greeted by the Info-Pang in the lower right corner of your screen.  This section briefly explains the Info-Pang and how to use him.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000652	What is it?
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000653	The Info-Pang will guide you through all of the basics including controls, hotkeys, menus, and even some game functions.  Once you have completed a section, you can always access it if you need to review it.  Simply right click on the Info-Pang and select Check the List.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000654	Access the Info-Pang
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000655	The Info-Pang will be activated by default when you log into the game.  If you would like to turn the Info-Pang off, Right Click on the Info-Pang and select Hide.  If later you would like to recall the Info-Pang you can do that by accessing the Start Menu, selecting Helper, and then selecting Info-Pang.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000656	Duel among users
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000657	This is a duel between 2 players.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000658	PvP
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000659	It means a fight between characters by mutual agreement. Affects PVP fame and PVP point.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000660	Asking for PvP
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000661	If you right-click with ALT key on the player whom you want to have duel with, you can have a duel with the player in case of that the user accepts that.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000662	In case of that you are the leader of your troupe and the clicked one is another leader of other troupe, you can have a group duel, if the other lead accept it.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000663	The result of PVP and Fame
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000664	PVP fame and PVP point change according to PvP record.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000665	placholder 49
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000666	placholder 50
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000667	placholder 51
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000668	placholder 52
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000669	placholder 53
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000670	placholder 54
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000671	placholder 55
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000672	placholder 56
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000673	placholder 57
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000674	placholder 58
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000675	placholder 59
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000676	placholder 60
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000677	placholder 61
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000678	placholder 62
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000679	placholder 63
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000680	placholder 64
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000681	placholder 65
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000682	placholder 66
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000683	Server
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000684	Guild bank and Guild sieges are available only at the 1st sub server of each server set.
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000685	placholder 67
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000686	placholder 68
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000687	placholder 69
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000688	placholder 70
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000689	placholder 71
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000690	placholder 72
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000691	placholder 73
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000692	placholder 74
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000693	placholder 75
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000694	placholder 76
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000695	placholder 77
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000696	placholder 78
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000697	placholder 79
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000698	placholder 80
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000699	placholder 81
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000700	placholder 82
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000701	placholder 83
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000702	placholder 84
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000703	placholder 85
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000704	Although Knights are capable of using all weapons that a Mercenary can use, to unlock their true potential they will need to wield the larger two handed Axes and Swords. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000705	Blades hold to a simple philosophy: "Hit hard, hit fast and never look back." Blades do not have class specific weapons they may use any Mercenary weapon. 
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000706	placholder 88
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000707	placholder 89
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000708	placholder 90
IDS_CLIENT_HELP_INC_000709	placholder 91